

I am a developer with more than 3 years of experience in web and mobile applications, covering both frontend and backend development. My experience extends to technologies such as React, Angular, PrimeFaces, Spring Boot, Java and Flutter. Additionally, I have experience managing MySQL and PostgreSQL databases, as well as using version control with GitHub.



# CONTACT

Cell phone: (57) 302-242-2101 Mail: dmortizcal@gmail.com Web: dmortizcal-dev.web.app



#### **SKILLS**

- TypeScript
- GitHub
- Angular
- JavaScript
- PostgreSQL
- React
- MySQL

- Java
- Flutter
- Spring Boot
- WordPress

# DANIEL MARIO ORTIZ CALDERÓN



## WORK EXPERIENCE

#### Developer

### Solredes SAS | Oct 2020 - Currently

- Development of mobile applications with Flutter for the municipality of Sopó and Transpremier LLC.
- Development of an administrative suite created in Angular and Spring Boot for the municipality of Sopó.
- Management of Wildfly servers to deploy applications.
- Development of SICO web application for the Regional Autonomous Corporation of La Guajira in Java and PrimeFaces.

#### **Information Analyst**

#### Carvajal Technology and Services | Jun 2015 - Aug 2016

- Reception of documentation, analysis and response for credit processes.
- Management of information system for credit disbursements.
- Digitization of the documentation received.

## **Telemarketing Assistant**

#### SRF Consultores - Gold Partner Microsoft Dynamics | Ene 2014 -Jul 2014

- Creation of microsites, to expand information on products or
- In charge of the FTP server, for transferring files to and from the server, creating addresses and uploading microsites.



## **EDUCATION**

# Universidad Distrital Francisco José de Caldas

**Telematics engineering** 

2023 - (Completed)

Universidad Distrital Francisco José de Caldas

**Technologist in Data Systematization.** 

2020 (Completed)

#### Servicio Nacional de Aprendizaje (SENA).

Technologist in Analysis and development of information systems.

2013 (Completed)